(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
(Space Rice Cake)
(KARINA joined the show as a part-timer.)
(This smart beginner...)
(handled everything from checking the dining area...)
(to doing the dishes.)
(With such a skilled part-timer on board,)
(the Seoul branch got on track.)
(And they achieved their dream goal of hitting 1,000 dollars in sales.)
(The ambitious owner revamped the menu.)
(Ghost pepper pizza)
(Goheung sea margarita)
(A customer said, "I heard you added pizza to the menu.")
(Word of the new menu item had already spread widely.)
(With their expectations fully met, the customers were satisfied.)
(While the business was booming,)
(a very special guest arrived at Space Rice Cake.)
(Ms. Yang!)
(Hee Eun came to Space Rice Cake.)
(I'd like a shrimp burger, please!)
(Hee Eun's table: 1 shrimp burger combo,)
(1 original tteokbokki, 1 pomegranate ade)
(Coming right up. We'll have that ready for you shortly.)
(Okay!)
Shrimp burger, tteokbokki, and pomegranate ade.
(While repeating the order to herself, she runs into...)
- Oh, my. - The cutlery is...
available upstairs.
- Please put this on your table. - Yes.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Customers keep pouring in.)
One tteokbokki, one pomegranate ade,
and one shrimp burger.
One beef burger, one tteokbokki,
one pizza, one cake,
and one non-alcoholic margarita.
Yes.
One ade, one carrot cake,
one tteokbokki, and one beef burger.
(Main Dish Order Status)
(1 shrimp burger, 2 beef burgers,)
(3 orders of tteokbokki, 2 orders of pizza)
We have three orders of tteokbokki in total, right, Yu Jin?
Yes, that's correct.
(The kitchen is working at full capacity.)
Did you cut the pizza?
- We have three burgers to make. - No, I didn't cut it.
Can't I cut it after putting it on the plate?
- Can I just move it as it is? - Put it on the plate,
cut it, and add basil leaves...
- and cheese. That's how you do it. - Okay.
- So I should move it first. - The basil shouldn't be cut.
- Mi Hyun. - Take them out and add them later.
Yes?
- We have three burgers to make. - Okay.
- I'll do that. - Please do it for me.
You do the rest.
(While Mimi is preparing burgers...)
This is the pizza for Table Four.
Tables 4 and 6.
What is wrong with you, pizza?
What is wrong with you?
(She handles the situation perfectly and prepares the pizza properly.)
Hello. Here's your pizza.
(The pizza is served immediately.)
(Having a bite of the pizza)
The pizza dough is rice cake.
(A Taiwanese customer with an incredibly sharp palate is here.)
The dough is incredibly chewy and nice.
It's so chewy and tasty.
(The mother who can handle spicy food well...)
(Hissing)
It's too spicy for me.
(And the father who can't handle spicy food)
(Eun Ji is making a pomegranate ade for Hee Eun.)
- Ms. Yang. - You have a lot of customers.
Thank you for taking time...
out of your busy schedule. It means a lot to us.
Really? I came straight here right after finishing a live show...
- and a recording session. - Thank you so much.
- This is yuzu radish pickle. - Yes.
(Impressed)
Yu Jin and I made it.
- You did? - Yes. Please try it.
This will be an unforgettable experience for you guys.
- Absolutely. Yes. - Right?
- Right. - We're experiencing something new.
(Eun Ji leaves to continue making unforgettable life experiences.)
(Hee Eun tastes the pomegranate ade.)
It's nice.
Two beef burgers and three orders of tteokbokki.
(The head chef feels rushed as always.)
(She puts 3 pots of tteokbokki on the stove.)
I'm going to make beef burgers now.
(She starts cooking 2 beef patties at the same time.)
(While the patties are sizzling to perfection,)
(Eun Ji is heading somewhere with a shaker in her hands.)
(Hee Eun shakes her hand too.)
I make margarita too, Ms. Yang.
(This former clown is multi-talented.)
- It's not easy, though. - It does seem hard.
Yes, it is.
Thank you.
(She's heading back after her little performance.)
The carrot cake came out first, again.
(As always, Yu Jin works busily...)
(to get the carrot cakes ready.)
(Thanks to her, the dessert always takes 1st place.)
The carrot cake...
(Her carrot cake making system keeps improving.)
Two pots of original tteokbokki are ready to go.
- It's hot. - Okay.
Ms. Yang.
You guys are really amazing.
Here's your tteokbokki.
The pot is really hot.
Okay. Got it.
- Please don't touch the pot. - Okay.
Your tteokbokki is out first.
- The rest is coming right up. - Okay. Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Here are the original tteokbokki and the carrot cake you ordered.
Please have some yuzu radish pickle with the other dishes.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Having her first bite of tteokbokki)
(Nodding in satisfaction)
(Eun Ji has finished decorating the margarita.)
(She enters the dining area with the margarita.)
(Looking around)
(Wandering around)
Excuse me.
Here's your...
non-alcoholic margarita.
You ordered this, right?
- Yes. - Yes?
Did you not order it?
One ade... I'll go upstairs...
to make the margarita and come back down.
- No orders are ready yet, right? - Right.
The margarita is for Table Six.
(She excitedly headed to the margarita station.)
(She made the drink.)
(While putting on her little performance,)
(she completely forgot the table number.)
- You didn't order this? - No.
Which table ordered this?
Yu Jin, which table is this for?
The table over there on the far left.
It must be Table Six.
- What was the table number? - We still need to check...
- if they ordered it. - Oh, you're right, Yu Jin.
- Is it the right table? - Yes, it is.
- Use this to cut the rice cake. - Margarita.
- Thank you. - Goheung sea margarita!
Margarita!
Cheers.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
It has no alcohol in it.
- Thank you. - Enjoy.
(Hello)
Ms. Yang is having the tteokbokki right now.
Is she enjoying it?
Yes, she likes it very much.
I'm glad to hear that.
(Hissing)
It's spicy, but it's nice.
(She's enjoying it.)
We're still missing two of our dishes.
(Meanwhile, these customers haven't touched their food.)
(After their food was served earlier...)
(Let's wait until all of our dishes are out.)
(They agreed to hold off on eating to take photos of all of the food.)
(We're still missing the pizza and something else.)
(The pizza is on its way out, so you can take photos.)
Oh, the pizza is ready.
- One more shrimp burger coming up. - Great.
(Topping the pizza with basil)
(Grating cheese on top of the pizza as a final touch)
I'll show you something cool.
- Nice. - The shell game.
Which one is real?
Both are beef.
(After Young Ji's adorable little show...)
Nice.
Two beef burgers and one shrimp burger are ready.
Hello.
- You ordered pizza, right? - Yes.
- Here's your beef burger. - The burger is here.
Please enjoy.
(They finally take photos of their dishes.)
(And they officially dig in!)
Oh, I see. It's rice cake.
- I see. - That's why it's chewy.
- You're right. - It's rice cake.
This one is my favorite.
(The taste is worth the wait.)
Here's your shrimp burger.
Oh, this is it. The serving size is big.
Yes, it's quite big.
- Do you like the tteokbokki? - I didn't know... It's good.
- It's a bit spicy, though. - It's a bit spicy, isn't it?
- Yes, but it's tasty. - Do you like it?
- It's deliciously spicy. - I'm glad to hear that.
Here are your tteokbokki and burger.
The tteokbokki is very hot, so I recommend not touching...
- Please don't touch the pot. - Okay.
- Thank you. - I'll bring you tongs and scissors.
(With the original tteokbokki served last...)
It's cute.
(All orders are cleared!)
(Meanwhile, Hee Eun finished her meal.)
- I'd like to settle up now. - Absolutely.
- Ms. Yang, how was the food? - Ms. Yang, why don't you...
- It was good. - come in and have a look around?
I'd love to.
Seriously, this is...
- This is so fun. - Awesome.
You guys must be...
- really exhausted right now. - We're fine.
Young Ji said she was losing hair...
and asked for some bandanas.
- That's right. - Ms. Yang, thank you so much.
(It was Day 2 in Goheung, when they were closed for the day.)
Can you just ask Ms. Yang Hee Eun to send us some bandanas?
- Let's send her a video message. - Okay. I'll speak politely.
(They recorded a video message right away.)
Hello, Ms. Yang. I am Lee Young Ji.
I've been enjoying wearing the glasses you gave me.
I'm starting to lose hair right now.
So, if it's not too much to ask,
could you please send us some of the bandanas...
or handkerchiefs you have? We'd much appreciate it...
and really enjoy wearing them.
Ms. Yang, I love you.
Everyone, say, "I love you." Ready, go.
- I love you! - I love you! You're the best.
- Like this? - There you go.
- You know what I mean, right? - Yes.
The front part should take up a bigger portion...
because this section pulls back over your head.
Then, pull it tightly and tie it at the back of your head. Okay?
- This is nice. - Okay, Young Ji. Let's do this.
- Good. And then... - It fits me perfectly.
I pulled it over your head.
(You should pull the front section backward over your head.)
- That's how you wear it. - I like this. I look cute.
I like this.
- It's nice, Ms. Yang. - Thank you, Ms. Yang.
- Thank you. - You're the best, Ms. Yang.
- Thank you. - Oh, please.
You just needed a mom's touch.
- A mom's touch. - I needed Ms. Yang's touch.
That's great.
- Choose your favorite color. - It's really nice.
- Yes. Thank you. - There are four different kinds.
- Thank you, Ms. Yang. - I'll keep all of them to myself.
Give her a hug.
- Come over here. - I'm covered in oil. I'm sorry.
- I'm covered in oil. - Don't worry about it.
- You've got this. - We've got this.
I was going to just give you these, but I ate your food too.
But the food was good.
- Really? - The food tasted good.
You should take it seriously when you actually charge people money.
- Absolutely. - Always.
- Thank you. - I'll text you, Ms. Yang.
- Okay. - Go home safely.
- Go home safely. - Keep up the good work.
Thank you, Ms. Yang.
- Make sure to be thorough. - Yes, Ms. Yang.
- We'll be thorough! - Ahk!
- Honesty, humility. Ahk. - Ahk!
- Thank you. - Go home safely, Ms. Yang.
- Have a great day. Bye. - Thank you.
These bandanas are the best.
(The next group of customers enter.)
Oh, my.
Welcome.
Here is the menu for you.
(While Eun Ji takes a new order...)
(The kitchen has cleared all the previous orders.)
(Young Ji doesn't seem to be feeling well.)
Later at break time...
(As a matter of fact, Young Ji...)
Is heartburn also a symptom of burnout?
It's possible to get it due to excessive work stress.
We got a new order.
(The examples of work stress)
(On top of that, she has to endure hot steam and smoke.)
- Maybe you have an upset stomach. - I don't know. I feel so queasy.
Young Ji, if you're thirsty, drink some sparkling water.
If you're feeling unwell, go sit down for a bit.
I'm fine. I can do this. Please take orders for now.
I'm really fine. I'm okay.
- How about you go see a doctor? - No. I'm fine.
- You really don't look so good. - I look a bit pale, don't I?
Your table number is nine. The cutlery is available upstairs.
(Table 9: Tteokbokki, shrimp burger combo, pizza, carrot cake, ade)
You have to be honest about how sick you are, Young Ji.
- Eun Ji is right. - I'm really fine.
- Are you feeling better now? - Yes.
Drink some sparkling water.
- We have one shrimp burger to make. - Okay.
(Mimi starts deep-frying a shrimp patty.)
Spray it.
(And then, she oversees the pizza prep.)
Nice.
(Yu Jin is prepping the pizza.)
(She spreads the special sauce evenly.)
The original tteokbokki.
(She grabs a strainer for the sauce.)
- I'll take a quick bathroom break. - Okay.
- We have some digestive medicine. - Okay.
(She's taking a quick break in the end.)
- Does she have an upset stomach? - I think so. She ate in a hurry.
I'm worried about her.
(Even though Young Ji is gone for a bit,)
(the kitchen keeps on rolling.)
(Mimi moves faster to cover for Young Ji.)
(Prepping a full load of tater tots)
(Prepping a full load of fried seafood)
(4 glasses of pomegranate ade are ready to go too.)
- Are you okay, Young Ji? - I'm good.
Let me just finish making the tteokbokki real quick.
Wait, stop. Take a five-minute break.
Table Nine.
(Fortunately, Eun Ji buys some time by serving the drinks.)
(Table 9: 4 pomegranate ade)
(The shrimp patty is ready too.)
(The dishes are coming out without a hitch.)
- Rest a bit. Take it easy. - Okay.
But let me just finish the tteokbokki. It's on the stove.
Staying here makes me feel more anxious.
(It's actually boiling vigorously.)
(She turns off the stove.)
Is it okay to keep this as it is?
(She sneaks out despite the staff's advice.)
- Sorry. I'll wrap it up real quick. - That's okay.
Don't apologize.
- Don't apologize. - There's no rush.
There's no rush.
(The rest of the dishes already came out.)
- It's okay. - It's okay.
- Everything else is out, right? - Yes.
- Just the tteokbokki is left? - I'll clean up here.
- Yes, just the tteokbokki is left. - For Table Nine.
Hello.
Hello. Let me take your order.
Young Ji, take your time. It's all pointless if you're sick.
- It's just... Earlier... - The business or whatever.
Make me look like a professional psychopath who's sick.
We got a new order.
Yes.
One non-alcoholic margarita, one ade,
one cake, one shrimp burger combo, and one tteokbokki.
- Let's do this! - Let's do this!
Honesty, humility. Aek.
Ahk.
Is the tteokbokki almost ready?
- It's coming out. - All right.
I feel bad that the tteokbokki came out late.
- I'm giving them extra fried sides. - Give them extra fried sides.
I put extra effort into this.
- It's even more beautiful. - Isn't it?
- It's even more beautiful. - Thank you.
- It's legendary, Young Ji. - I paid extra attention to it.
Here's Lee Young Ji's original tteokbokki.
Margarita.
(She walks in cheerfully to make margarita.)
Sparkling water.
(She carefully opens the cap.)
Here we go.
(The sparkling water fizzes over.)
Water bomb.
Water show.
(Eun Ji's enchanting performance)
(But there's no one here to watch it.)
(After mixing it well...)
Margarita.
(She pours the margarita into a glass with a sugar rim.)
The margarita for Table Ten
(With a slice of lemon, it's complete.)
Margarita.
Try it. It has no alcohol in it.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(The earlier wave of customers is heading out.)
- Did you enjoy the food? - Yes.
- Go home safely. - I liked the tteokbokki the most.
- Goodbye. - Thank you.
(The fact that the customers leave 1 by 1 only means...)
(Space Rice Cake)
(It only means a new wave is coming!)
Welcome.
We love you to space and back. Welcome to Space Rice Cake.
Can I get the name for the reservation?
It's under Kim Jan Di, and I booked for 1pm.
- Ms. Kim Jan Di? - Yes.
Almost paradise
- Are you adding a pomegranate ade? - Yes.
Understood.
Hello. Let me take your order.
Is the serving size of tteokbokki big?
It's a good size for 1 to 2 people.
- The shrimp burger is ready. - Okay.
Is the tteokbokki coming out, Chef Lee?
Jung Hye, the tteokbokki is coming right up.
I promised to make sure she wouldn't have to work hard like this.
You promised me...
I wouldn't even have to lift a finger.
The tteokbokki is ready.
Here's your shrimp burger.
Too much rice cake in a burger
Plump shrimp pop
(They don't know how to react.)
- Thank you. - Thank you. I love you.
Too much rice cake in a burger
(This customer is deeply moved and lost for words.)
Plump shrimp pop
Please come on up.
We serve house-made burgers. It's nice to meet you all.
A party of three coming upstairs.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Byeon Woo Seok, Seo Kang Jun, and Byun Yo Han...
are heading up to the second floor. Thank you.
(Tapping)
(However, there's a problem.)
(Traces of the previous customers still remain.)
(Here...)
(and there)
I'll clean it up for you.
Let me wipe the table.
Did you already take your seats? I'm very sorry.
I sincerely apologize once again.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for making you sit at such a dirty table.
I'll wipe it for you quickly.
Gosh, you're very kind.
I wanted to let you know that it's complete mayhem downstairs.
Should I take care of it?
- Stay right there, sir. - I'm sorry.
How could I make such a valued customer do this?
Please stay seated.
- Head Chef. - Yes?
It looks like upstairs isn't getting cleaned properly.
- It's mayhem. - Eun Ji.
- Yes? - We got a complaint...
about the cleaning upstairs.
Oh, my gosh.
You know the middle-aged guy who works part-time...
- for 16 dollars? - Yes.
Would you like him to help you?
Tell him to go upstairs now.
(Thinking hard)
Could he clear 5 tables for 3 dollars?
Sixteen dollars is so expensive.
(Reluctant to spend the money)
(It's too late to back out. He's coming to work.)
(The middle-aged part-timer comes in.)
Too much rice cake in a burger
I heard that you were hiring.
Is this the right place?
- Could you please clean up? - Yes.
Where?
The customers upstairs are finished eating.
But I've never done it before.
I have to learn from Eun Ji.
Learn what?
- Cleaning up? - I've only washed dishes.
Take a tray upstairs...
and clear everything off the tables.
Give the customers a bright, beautiful smile.
- Hurry up. - Where's the tray?
You'll find it upstairs.
(After getting pushed out the door, he turns around.)
Shouldn't I wipe the tables?
(She's too busy to answer.)
Yeong Seok, hurry up.
(Laughing)
She told me to clean up.
Hello. Thank you.
Yu Jin, is there...
You'll find a tray. Thank you.
(Like his senior told him, he's off to find a tray.)
(The youngest member stares into the void.)
Hello. It's nice to meet you, our new part-timer.
I didn't learn how to do this.
You just need to wipe the table.
Don't I have to spray anything?
Don't worry about that. I'll take care of it at the end.
If you find anything like this, bring it downstairs.
- Okay, what about this? - Yes.
Just leave it.
Is it supposed to be here?
Your presence is...
making things more complicated.
Gosh, it came out really well.
- Is that ready to go out? - Just serve honey with it.
(She takes some honey and gets ready to head out.)
The carrot cake needs to go out.
I'm so busy that I can barely think.
(She serves the pizza first fast.)
Here's your pizza.
Enjoy your food.
(Rushing back)
(There's so much to do.)
Hello. I'll take your order.
- The beef burger is ready. - Okay.
I'll take your order.
We'd like...
We have another order.
One pomegranate ade, one carrot cake,
one pizza, one tteokbokki, and one beef burger, please.
Okay.
- Yeong Seok. - Yes?
On your way upstairs,
take tteokbokki and beef burger combo to Table 12.
- Table 12? - Yes.
I'm sorry. You must be disappointed that I'm here.
Not at all. I'm happy to see you.
They're very busy downstairs.
- Here's your tteokbokki. Enjoy. - Thank you.
(While the new server fills in the gaps)
I should've made a lot of carrot cake earlier.
- Are you ready to order? - Yes.
Too much rice cake in a burger.
Two margaritas.
- Okay. - One pomegranate ade.
- That'd be all. - Okay.
Isn't Chicago on the menu?
We're discussing whether to add Chicago to the menu or not.
I'll do my best to put it on the menu.
Thank you.
(Doing her best immediately)
(I've got six armor)
(You've got a white toothbrush)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
We have an order.
One pizza, one beef burger,
one carrot cake, two margaritas...
Eun Ji, you should get paid for your performance.
- Right. - Why do you keep performing...
without getting paid 9.9 dollars?
I just gave them a sneak peek.
How much are we losing because of that?
It was only a sneak peek.
(The part-timer is wandering around without knowing what to do.)
We need more side plates.
The gray... I mean, the silver ones.
(He got it.)
(He's still following orders to a T.)
(Letting the youngest run on autopilot)
Table 12, soda and pomegranate.
We're missing glasses for pomegranate ade.
For now, I brought three glasses for pomegranate ade.
Where should I put them?
You're so smart.
You brought them out as soon as I asked.
Washing dishes is my specialty.
- You're very impressive. - Thank you, thank you.
(Thanks to him, things are slowly coming together.)
This is for Table 11, that's for Table 12.
Do you need help?
Please take these to Table 11.
(On the verge of a wrong order disaster)
(Table 11, 1 mint carrot cake)
- Your pizza... It's not for you. - No.
- Is this for you? - No.
- They're eating pizza at Table 11. - Carrot cake...
- I'll give you carrot cake first. - Carrot cake is for Table 11.
- This is for another table. - Table 12?
- Please go this way. - Is it Table 12?
- This is our new menu item today. - That's right.
- Could you explain it to them? - It's warm.
Ghost pepper pizza!
(My goodness...)
It's made with the hottest peppers...
in the world called ghost pepper.
- We ordered one Coke. - Nice to meet you.
- Do you want 1 more? - We ordered 1 more.
One more? I'll bring it to you right away. I'm sorry.
- You have to bow at a perfect 90°. - Okay.
We sincerely apologize.
- It's coming right up. - Thank you.
I love you.
(1 ghost pepper pizza, 1 mint carrot cake, 1 pomegranate ade)
- I got hungry after sitting here. - Me too.
I can smell the food.
Thank you.
(Remaining Order Status)
(Chef Mimi starts with the pizza.)
(Making two at the same time)
(While she's busy making the pizza)
This is insane.
These three are insane.
(Young Ji's task 1: Tteokbokki)
(Young Ji's task 2: Beef patty)
(Young Ji's task 3: Tater tots)
- Please sprinkle some salt. - Okay.
(Seasoning with salt)
You're amazing.
(Encouraged by Mimi's compliment,)
(she also puts a burger together.)
The world I'm living in is...
insane.
(Filling the basket with tater tots)
It's hot.
(Once it's quickly placed on the tray,)
(Eun Ji finishes making an ade on time.)
- Yes, it's for Table 13. - Okay.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Table 13. - It's for us.
This is pomegranate ade.
- Thank you. - Enjoy your food.
- It came out so fast. - He seems very shy.
Right, he got so embarrassed.
Goodness.
I haven't done this before.
(Laughing)
Let me watch you work for a while.
How many days have you been working?
My part-time job...
I've worked part-time a few times,
- but I never worked regularly. - Really?
Then you should work a few more years before serving margaritas.
Yes, I'd be happy just with cleaning.
You need to work longer.
- There's a nice view. - Yes.
The house next door has a traditional tiled roof.
Who has time to look outside right now?
Go out and ask if customers need anything.
Ask them if they got all their orders.
That part-timer...
We're insanely busy.
Why is he looking outside when we're drowning with work?
Is there anything you're waiting on?
We're waiting on our pizza and tteokbokki.
Pizza and tteokbokki? They'll be coming soon.
Hello.
- Did you get everything? - Yes, we got everything.
- Did you get everything? - Yes.
- How does it taste? - It's very good.
Do you like it? I'm glad.
(Keeping an eye on him after sending him out)
Are you enjoying your food?
Is everything okay?
- The food is great. - Really? I'm glad to hear that.
- Enjoy your food. - Good luck with work.
Is this for real?
(Feeling dizzy)
- I asked everyone. - What did they say?
Some got all their order, and some didn't.
(What did you do?)
- Really? - Yes.
- Gosh, Eun Ji. - You're working hard.
There's some hazing around here.
(Being a middle-aged rookie is rough.)
I'm sorry, but could you go upstairs...
and check who didn't get this?
- Shouldn't I take it with me? - These are pickles.
- Yes, that's a good idea. - Okay.
(He trudges upstairs after getting orders from his senior.)
Did you get this?
- No. - You didn't, right?
This is our basic side dish.
Our server Eun Ji probably forgot to serve you.
- Thank you. - Enjoy.
(However...)
(Yuzu radish pickles never made it to the tables.)
Didn't we order two?
- Excuse me, director. - Yes?
We ordered two margaritas,
- but one of them isn't here yet. - Okay.
- I'll go and scold them. - Wait, no...
I'll be right back.
(After realizing Eun Ji's mistake, he walks off with excitement.)
They ordered two margaritas,
but they only got one.
- They're complaining a lot. - Which table?
Did you see which number it was?
You're making it very hard for me.
Which table is it?
It's close to the wall. I didn't check the number.
That can happen.
Also, it's embarrassing to ask them...
about the pickles.
- Why? - No one got them.
They need to go out now. Come here.
Go and serve the pickles to the ones who didn't get them.
Hurry up. Here you go.
- Go. - I'll take this off.
- Give me 1 or 2. - Wait.
- Nothing is organized. - Give me 2 or 3.
(Middle-aged man is coming right up.)
This is pickled radish that comes with the dish.
Have some when the food gets too greasy.
Please have some even if you're almost done.
- We'll eat it as a dessert. - Okay.
Thank you.
(Eun Ji makes the omitted margarita.)
(She heads out with the shaker.)
Customer Number 14.
I apologize for the delay.
In front of you...
(My heart fluttered a little)
(Singing)
(Intense)
My goodness.
(Her butt was way too close.)
(Excuse me)
(And...)
(1 person giving her a piercing glare)
Don't look so serious.
(Grinning)
(Cheering her on with a forced smile)
This should be done. I'm very sorry.
No, it's okay.
(Once she fills up the glass)
Margarita!
This is Goheung sea margarita.
- Thank you. - Senorita.
Senorita.
- Was that all right? - You're something else.
(The kitchen is powering through the last orders.)
(Exhausted)
We can do this.
This headscarf is too small for me.
- It left a mark on your forehead. - It hurts so much.
(It squeezed her head the entire shift.)
It hurts a lot.
It's not that bad for me.
It's not even coming off of my head.
(Gosh, my head...)
At this rate, even Ms. Yang would...
- understand. - Right.
This is our last order.
I'll give more shrimp as you said.
That sounds good.
(The last beef burger is also ready.)
(And the carrot cake)
- Shall we go upstairs together? - Yes, please.
- Okay. - Thank you.
(Heading upstairs with the head chef)
This is great.
- This is the last order. - That's great.
Hello.
(1 original tteokbokki, 1 beef burger combo, 1 mint carrot cake)
- Thank you. - It's really delicious.
Yu Jin made this carrot cake.
- Thank you. - Enjoy your food.
Thank you.
(Exclaiming)
We gave it everything we had.
(Everyone starts catching their breath.)
I'll have it until tomorrow.
(I'll have this mark until tomorrow.)
It comes off when I scrub it immediately.
(Some serious cleanup after the lunch service)
(Eun Ji starts tidying up the dining area.)
(Yu Jin does the final check.)
(Then she suddenly rushes out.)
(1 margarita is sitting there in plain sight.)
I'm that, I'm that girl
(Our Margarita Girl is just enjoying herself.)
Please let her know that margarita didn't go out...
to Table 15.
(The youngest's final run)
(She appears.)
Move out of the way.
- She told me to tell you... - Yes?
that 1 margarita wasn't served to Table 15.
- Do it again and you're in trouble. - Why didn't it go out?
- A margarita didn't go out? - Right, at Table 15.
I sincerely apologize...
for the missed margarita order.
- It's okay. - When a margarita takes this long,
we don't serve it normally.
You don't have to do that.
Sure, we'd love to see it.
(Performing after getting permission)
(The kind customers play along.)
(Can you keep up?)
- It should be done. - Thank you.
Shall I shake it a little more?
Sure. Yes.
(She starts again right away.)
It's done.
- It wasn't easy. - Thank you.
(The Goheung sea in a glass)
- The color is pretty. - It really is.
(An ending way too dramatic for the performance)
I apologize for the delay once again.
- It's okay. - Don't worry.
- Thank you. - Enjoy.
(Just like that, Eun Ji's gala show is over.)
Thank you.
Stay strong.
- I'm coming through. - Bye.
We can do it.
(The customers start to head out 1 by 1.)
- Mi Hyun. - Yes?
I'm getting scared about the dinner service.
(The lunch service is over.)
Young Ji, I asked for a mat so that you can lie down...
in the pantry, so please wait.
I don't have to lie down.
- Come quickly. - I'll be there in a second.
Is your indigestion any better?
I'm losing my mind. I feel like I'm dying.
Seriously?
I feel terrible every time I spray oil.
What about pricking your finger?
We just need a needle.
- The old-school finger pricking? - Yes.
That's a good idea.
- Have a seat here. - Sit down.
- You'd feel better if I press here. - Start, Young Ji.
- Right? - No.
- I don't want to. - Prick this side first.
No!
Pricking this spot is the most...
- Bring me a needle. - Isn't it effective?
All right.
I'll just massage you.
(While Young Ji is causing a scene)
(The pantry situation is reported in the production staff group chat.)
(We're going to prick Young Ji's finger.)
(Come and grab the lancet.)
(The first-aid kit is coming to the rescue.)
You got some foundation on.
It's pricked.
- It doesn't hurt, right? - Blood is coming out.
Strangely, I think I feel better...
after getting my finger pricked.
Is it just in my head?
- Girls, let's go. - Let's do this.
We can do it.
Everyone, please wash your hands.
Okay.
Try not to splash so much water on the floor.
The business never ends.
- It's no joke. - Seriously.
Two more days until I become human again.
I'm not human right now.
- Young Ji. - Yes?
We set up what you asked for.
- What? - Remember what you wanted?
What?
- What did you say? - It's Goheung.
(Goheung?)
It's the Goheung sea.
(It was two days ago.)
Director.
Could you put a seaside background here?
- Behind us? - Yes.
- This is seriously... - Right here?
stressing me out.
I might get a burnout already.
(Just as the head chef wished, this beautiful view of Goheung)
(Copied and pasted in Seoul)
Thank you.
- Thank you. - To commemorate it,
I'll do a performance.
(Want to go see the ocean?)
(Baby)
(Along the seat next to us, down)
(A celebration performance that's exhausting to watch)
(I prefer to go to Goheung)
My gosh.
It's Goheung.
What's important is that I don't look this way.
They should've put it on the floor.
I don't look at the floor either.
Could you change this instead?
Draw a picture and paint over it.
(The head chef's field of vision got much narrower.)
Yu Jin, can you measure the yuzu dongchimi?
- Let's start with the dough. - Okay.
All right, let's do our job.
Do you think we'll miss this moment someday?
Won't it get romanticized with time and become something we miss?
Do you think we'll actually miss this?
When we start missing it,
let's hurry up and do Season Two.
Let's open our third branch.
- It will come true again. - No way.
- Who? Me? - Yes.
Who else would do it other than you?
Chef, how many days have we been working?
- It's been over a week. - It's been over a week,
and how does it feel?
It feels terrible.
(Her unfiltered and honest response)
What's the hardest part?
It's hardest when I feel like I'm not improving.
You must really love cooking.
What about the employees? How are you doing?
It's hard but fun.
Is it fun?
(Even she feels awkward saying it.)
There's no way this is fun.
If you're having fun doing this, something is seriously wrong.
Go.
While stretching it out...
Okay. There it is.
- Two more. - Okay.
(The kitchen team prepares the pizza dough.)
(Everyone is focusing quietly on their own work.)
(Laughing)
(Chuckling)
(Smiling)
(A bitter laugh at the endless prep cycle)
(Moaning)
(Screaming)
Do you want to hear how much we made this afternoon?
- How much? - To cheer you up?
- Yes. - Yes.
I bet lunch sales were quite good.
- I will tell you. - Including pizzas, right?
Today's lunch sales were insane.
Let's hear how insane they were.
- Lunch sales were 884 dollars. - Gosh.
- My gosh. - That's great.
Let's go for 1,500 dollars.
(Lunch service sales)
(12 beef burger combos, 9 shrimp burger combos,)
(14 original tteokbokki, 10 ghost pepper pizzas,)
(14 mint carrot cakes, 7 Goheung sea margaritas...)
(Total lunch sales, 884 dollars)
The biggest seller was...
ghost pepper pizza.
Ghost pepper pizza!
Yes, that's what sold the most today.
(Looking gloomy)
That's not the problem.
It's completely burnt. I'm in trouble.
I'm sorry.
- It's okay. - I burnt one.
I'll eat this for dinner.
Let's eat it together.
Let's make one. I'm hungry.
- What do you think? - Actually, it looks okay.
- Yes, let's make one. - You said that it's burnt.
(How does it look okay?)
Should we make one or not?
- Let's make one. - Let's do it.
That sounds good, chef.
Let's give it to the part-timer when she comes.
(Peace restored after solving it with staff meal)
- Woman. - Woman, please wait.
A human woman.
(During the day, a warm and compassionate woman)
(She doesn't know the luxury of a coffee break)
(A hardworking woman)
(When night comes, she preps for dinner and goes to bed)
(That kind of hardworking woman)
(Lyrics steeped in the joys and hardships of a business)
- I'm a woman - I'm the head chef
(Head chef)
(You're a little rascal)
(The king)
(That's enough. Let's focus.)
When is the part-timer coming?
- The sauce is ready. - In any minute now.
When the part-timer gets here,
I'll train her.
- Okay. - That sounds good.
We're counting on you.
You were showing her who was boss yesterday.
During the handover.
How does it go? Too much...
- Too much rice cake in a burger - Too much rice cake in a burger.
Too much rice cake in a burger
She was laying down the law with that phrase.
I was showing her our energy and spirit.
From what I heard yesterday,
the person is close to me,
and they're also acquainted with Yu Jin. I have no idea.
Who is it?
The person will add some energy to this exhausted mood.
That's nice. I'm too exhausted now.
It must be here.
(Someone has arrived at the restaurant.)
Unbelievable.
(Laughing)
Do I go in?
(Striding straight to the restaurant)
(She enters without hesitation.)
Hello.
My goodness.
(They're glad to see her.)
(The savior of exhausted Space Rice Cake)
(The one-day part-timer is here.)
(The leader of La Chica, a trendy dance crew)
(The popular queen who has various charms)
(Today's part-timer, Gabee)
- Gabee is here. - She's wearing the uniform too.
- Hello. - How have you been?
- Hello. - Hello.
- I heard you needed a part-timer. - This is Mimi.
- She's very busy. - Hello, Mimi.
- Hello, nice to meet you. - Hello.
- Sorry, I can't stop halfway. - She has dough to work on.
- Hello, she's the head chef. - Hello.
- Hello. - You've become a chef?
- Yes. - Congratulations.
I can't believe this.
- Things are very chaotic, but... - Exactly.
- Come here. - We actually run the restaurant.
I'm sorry in advance.
I'm sorry, we'll be like this all day long.
Gabee, we can't say anything when the business starts.
- We really... - I hope you understand.
But I really like this kind of work.
- I like manual labor. - Really?
- Change with me starting tomorrow. - Even back then,
as I worked at a restaurant, I thought,
"This is what I should do when I retire."
Gosh, you said that.
It took my mind off things.
- That's right. - She keeps saying dangerous stuff.
(The birth of another mouth of terror)
- You're in for trouble. - Thoughts disappeared from my mind.
(Hurriedly filling up the hole)
(Looking around)
Why did you look behind... Did you make another hole?
(She has no excuse to make.)
Staff meal again?
- No. - Come here.
It's not staff meal at all.
Don't laugh, Director.
This is what I do for a living.
Please come and make the dough.
(Making the staff meal with the ruined dough)
You're making the staff meal already?
It's good to prepare in advance.
I won't put special effort into plating.
Gabee, please try the pizza.
- Thank you. - The plate is really hot.
- It's spicy. - It's spicy.
- It's spicy. - Be careful.
Do you eat Buldak?
- You bet. - Dip the sauce.
- It looks delicious. - Be careful, it's hot.
This is crazy. The dough is so hot.
It's hot. It's freshly-cooked sticky rice.
It's so hot.
(Since it's hot, Eun Ji feeds her.)
(Nodding)
(It makes her eyes open wide.)
- How is it? - Is it good, Gabee?
It's so good.
- Is it good? - Yes.
- This basil here. - Basil.
This is driving me crazy.
It's so delicious.
The rice cake and the dough are different.
I rolled out the dough.
(Please compliment me.)
Bits of everyone's soul are in it.
- It's so delicious. - Thank you.
It's a pity you're selling a limited amount.
Exactly.
You want me to make more?
(The kitchen team's sharp glares)
I'm sorry, but may I ask...
what kind of character you are?
I've lost my mind.
- I think you can stop now, Mimi. - This is the last one.
- Should I make one more? - No, let's not do a just-in-case.
- No. - Is this enough?
- Don't make it. - Can I really stop?
- Prepare the fritters now. - Okay.
(After acting all cocky, she caused an accident.)
(Patting it)
Do you...
- Mimi. - Give me a second.
(She left her post for just a second.)
- I made a mistake. - What?
I told you.
I'm sorry.
(Today's lesson: Don't act cocky.)
- Gabee, you must be busy. - At once.
- Not at all. - Thanks for coming.
Anything I can help? I want to do something.
- What should I hand you? - Shall we gather the energy?
Teach her the honesty humility cheer.
Honesty, humility, ahk.
When I say "honesty," you go "honesty."
- Humility, ahk. - Humility, ahk.
- We literally do it every day. - "Ahk?"
We're expecting a lot of customers today.
- To be honest, - The most customers ever.
if you happen to make a mistake,
- I might scold you unintentionally. - Of course.
Gabee.
Two eyes...
down.
- I might do this. - I'm sorry.
- "Gabee." - So please understand.
Don't worry.
You know it's nothing personal, right?
I majored in getting scolded.
- It's your major? - So don't worry.
Gabee.
(Silent)
Your shoulders down.
(Slumping)
- That's it. - Can't she lift them up for now?
- Shall we change it to "up?" - Get them up now.
- Gabee. - Yes!
Your shoulders up.
(Squaring their shoulders)
- Good. This is perfect. - Scoliosis.
- Okay. - This is how it goes.
Chef, how many more?
I told you to count. Did you not?
I told you I can't count.
What kind of a person in their 20s,
no, what kind of a 32-year-old cannot count?
(Oh, dear.)
As I'm grilling next to you, you should count!
One, two, three...
I'm sorry to do this with you here.
It's okay.
Eleven... I can't even count,
and how could you embarrass me in front of her?
- I'm sorry, Mimi. - I forgot how many I counted...
because I shouted at you.
(Flustered)
- One, two, three, four... - Eleven, counting the topmost one.
It's 11 including this?
(She's going mad because Mimi can't count.)
Twelve.
(The counting commotion passes.)
I'll start grilling the buns. Today's business starts.
(She starts grilling rice cake buns.)
Gabee, is your album releasing on the 20th?
Yes, on the 20th.
I read the news that you're releasing an album.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
How did you think to release your own album?
I should try everything I want.
- That's life. - How cool.
- I'm just doing it and enjoying it. - So cool.
- You only live once. - That's right.
My dear chef wanted to try running a restaurant...
and is having a burnout now.
Who are you talking about?
- Was this your dream, Chef? - I have no idea what you're saying.
(I have no idea what you're saying.)
I have a MOT. Do you know what it means?
- What is MOT? - Mouth of terror.
- Oh, mouth of terror. - Yes.
I know what you mean.
- I know. - In Goheung, she said,
"I want to go to Seoul."
"I want to go to Seoul." So we suddenly got dragged here.
Really? Because she said she wanted to?
- Yes. - That's scary.
They make your wish come true.
They remember everything you said.
A wish like "I want to earn ten million dollars" don't come true.
(Current time, 5:30pm)
Are they coming?
(She carefully turns the sign to "open.")
Come in, everyone.
(The dinner business starts.)
(The kitchen team is very serious as usual.)
(Charismatic)
- That was cool. - What was?
- I didn't do anything. - The way you put gijeongtteok in.
- It... - Let's kiss.
You say that anytime at random.
She's got issues too.
(She tries to calm down by kissing.)
The rice cake's condition is more important than mine.
That was really cool, wasn't it?
(Narcissistic)
Are they coming soon?
(Meanwhile, the new part-timer is excited.)
I'm curious.
- Various customers come. - Exactly.
Were there any moments that got you flustered?
- We can't see anything. - Right.
The service team... You'll get to experience a lot.
Me... Oh, is this outfit...
- for the servers? Okay. - Yes, the service team's uniform.
Things will be hectic.
(While the novice part-timer is nervous...)
- You're starting to feel nervous? - Yes.
- Hello. - Hello.
We have a new part-timer today too.
Hello, I'm Gabee.
Hello.
I love you as much as the space. Welcome to Space Rice Cake.
- Love you. - Yes.
- What's your name? - What's your name?
- Jeong Eun. - Ms. Kang Jeong Eun.
What time did you reserve?
Are you two dating?
I see, you're two couples on a date.
It's a double date.
Oh, my gosh.
- You guys look so cute. - Yes.
You're all 19, right?
- No, I'm 20. - I'm joking.
No way. I thought you were 19.
(The servers are very outgoing.)
Have a look at the menu.
The pizza was really delicious.
It's very spicy but delicious. You know what I mean?
It's super delicious and chewy.
Since the part-timer has tried it,
she's recommending the menus too. I like it.
That means they're ordering a pizza.
We'll have one each except the soft drinks.
I understand. You'll change it to an ade?
You're very witty. You're good.
(The senior is generous with her praises.)
Hello. Welcome.
I love you as much as the space. Welcome to Space Rice Cake. Hello.
(She copies her senior's greeting right away.)
(Meanwhile, the puppy eavesdrops on the orders.)
(A long face)
I don't welcome them.
I don't welcome them. Go out.
Dear viewers. Are you having fun?
Welcome.
Why do you act like you welcome them?
I welcome them wholeheartedly.
I couldn't welcome them more than this
One carrot cake which Yu Jin likes,
one pomegranate ade,
one margarita,
one pizza, one tteokbokki,
one shrimp burger, and one beef burger.
Okay. Mimi, we have two burgers.
- Okay. - Another ade.
(Table 1: Mint carrot cate, 1, pomegranate ade, 2)
- You can do it. - Here comes the order.
Two orders of non-alcohol Goheung sea margarita,
two carrot cakes, two orders of tteokbokki,
one shrimp burger and one beef burger.
Oh, gosh. I'm so nervous!
- You can do it. - You can do it.
(As learned, she adds pomegranate syrup)
(Heaps of ice too)
My gosh.
It's okay.
(Sparkling water refreshing enough to explode)
(Humming)
(The service master is having international diplomatic ties.)
This is how things were all this time.
(They're so used to it.)
She's good.
She's really good.
(Her diplomacy is admirable.)
Here's the order.
(She proudly enters with the order sheet.)
I respect you, Eun Ji.
Gabee, you're doing well.
Thank you. I'll do my best.
- You're cool. - I'll help.
(Pouring half-wasted sparkling water)
(The ade is ready.)
Thank you.
- I'll serve these two first. - Okay.
(The experienced server serves first.)
One... No, two glasses of pomegranate ade.
One Coke.
Pickled radish.
One margarita is on the way.
It'll be served without trouble.
- I'll give you nice ones first. - Okay.
(The rice cake buns are grilled well.)
Since it's confusing, I'll just give two.
Okay, just give me two.
Since you're weak with numbers.
Thank you.
- Honesty, humility, ahk. - Ahk.
(Beef patty enters too.)
(She starts grilling it seriously.)
(Press it hard to get the thickness right.)
Will the beef burger be ready soon?
- It's on the way. - Yes.
- Beef is on the way. - Shrimp is ready too.
I'll serve shrimp burger and beef burger together.
- Okay. - Beef burger is ready now.
The beef burger is ready.
(Dinner business' first beef burger)
Two glasses of pomegranate ade.
You're so fast.
You can do it.
Shin Gabee.
- Shin Gabee. - You knew I was a Shin too.
- You're a Shin? - Of course I knew.
I'm so touched, Young Ji.
You changed your name too.
How did you... You know well.
Of course.
(Boasting)
How do you know so well?
I know when I like someone.
- This is crazy. - I...
I know the names of everyone whom I want to kiss.
(She appeals to Cheol Yong.)
Hello.
- Tell me if you need anything. - Okay.
How's the pomegranate ade? You haven't tried yet, right?
- No. - I made it.
- Here. Enjoy your food. - Thank you.
Where are you from?
- China. - China.
- That's why she sang that just now. - Yes.
I don't know a Chinese song.
- It's okay. - I want to sing it to you.
I love you.
I love you too.
- Oh, my gosh, thank you. - You're pretty.
- That means "you're pretty!" - That's right.
Enjoy your food. Bye.
- Bye. - Thank you. Bye.
(Besides Cheol Yong, everyone has fallen for her.)
(Meanwhile, at the kitchen)
(Torn)
It's a bit crushed.
- What is? - This. What to do?
You can pile it up together. It's okay.
- Should I? - Yes.
If you're unhappy, grill a new one. It's okay.
(She tries to cover it up using cheese.)
Just be careful when you assemble it.
Beef is ready.
(It's complete for now.)
- It's crushed, so be careful. - Bring it here.
This.
This here.
- Please hide it well. - Okay.
It...
(A new menu is added every day in this kitchen.)
It's okay, this happened because there's a lot of meat.
(Today, a double beef burger is released.)
It's okay.
One beef burger and one shrimp burger.
(New menu, double beef burger, is released!)
This is shrimp burger.
(Table 1)
This is beef burger.
Enjoy.
Hello, I'm back.
(The novice part-timer serves burgers too.)
One beef, one shrimp. Here are the burgers.
Enjoy.
(As expected from a double date, they share the burgers.)
- It's hard to cut. - Why are you so deep in thought?
- You're struggling. - I can't cut it.
(He's buffering, either because of the double beef or the double date.)
(A bite of double beef)
(Humming)
(This side's couple tries it too.)
It's tasty.
It's so good.
(Double the love, double the meat juice)
It's delicious.
(She checks the order sheets to make sure no mistake was made.)
- Good job, Gabee. - Of course, Eun Ji.
Gabee, could you make one ade?
Yes, I will.
If something got on the side, wipe it with a kitchen towel.
Okay.
(She's preparing the next menu without a break.)
- Tteokbokki is ready. - Okay.
Young Ji really looks like a tteokbokki restaurant owner...
from the back.
Here comes tteokbokki.
Good. One each.
- Good. - Thank you, girl.
Here you go.
It's original tteokbokki.
Enjoy.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- The rice cake is so big. - It's like a python.
(Impressed by the rice cake coil)
It's delicious.
- It's delicious. - It's delicious.
It's so tasty.
Yes.
I think things are fine. It's relaxing.
- Why is it relaxing? - Don't even say that.
(After coming to Seoul, Young Ji learned to watch her mouth.)
Who's relaxed?
I need to grill this.
(As soon as she says that, customers enter.)
I love you as much as the space. Welcome to Space Rice Cake.
Would you like to order right away?
The orders are in.
One ade, one carrot cake,
one tteokbokki, and one beef burger combo.
One carrot cake, one pomegranate ade,
(Order Status)
(Carrot cakes, beef burgers, tteokbokki, pomegranate ades)
Do we...
(While the orders are pouring in...)
just go in?
It smells good.
(The round body shape looks familiar.)
The smell of burgers.
My gosh.
The master is here.
(The master is here.)
The master?
- Hello. - Hello, Manager.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello, nice to see you. - Hello.
- You didn't have to. - It's a present.
I baked it myself. It's cheesecake.
- Really? That's amazing. - You can have it later.
Thank you so much.
- She's my employee. - Really?
Nice to meet you.
- You can peek inside. - Can I?
Since you know how things are.
- You can come and see too. - Thank you.
Good luck.
- Hello. - Hello.
- I'll order. - He's here with a restaurant chef.
- Hello. With a restaurant chef? - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
You must know better as chefs,
but things are quite hectic.
- Neapolitan Matfia. - Yes.
- Order quickly. - Okay.
Once I give you this,
- go up and take a seat anywhere. - Oh, I order first?
He's paying, right?
- Of course he is. - Of course he is.
You charge your teacher?
- Of course we do. - Of course we do.
(Familiarity is nothing compared to the value of labor.)
Labor is labor.
We have a dream.
So we need to charge him.
Normally, they serve their teachers for free.
No way.
(Laughing)
You guys are strictly business.
- That'll be 25.8 dollars. - Okay.
Table Five...
is where the manager of new menu development is seated.
- Okay. - Okay.
One Lee Young Ji's original tteokbokki,
one too much rice cake in a burger, beef burger combo.
(The HQ manager's table)
He's so rich, but...
One-on-one... This is a mirror match.
Exactly. He's rich, so he could've ordered more.
He ordered those two?
- Okay. - He only ordered two.
- The teacher? - He didn't even order an ade.
He didn't even order an ade?
- Enter one ade into the POS system. - When your master comes,
you normally serve them stuff on the house.
But you don't do that?
We don't. Why'd we put it on the house?
- Eun Ji. - He's your teacher, though.
It doesn't matter.
The fritters are hot.
He only ordered one beef burger? Okay.
(Everyone is upset for some reason.)
- This is funny. - He's asking for a fight.
I think the manager...
just ordered these dishes...
to check out Young Ji's cooking.
(Meanwhile, the manager who threw the kitchen into chaos...)
It's my first time coming up here.
It's huge.
(is peacefully looking around the restaurant.)
- Can we sit anywhere? - What?
Why don't we sit here?
You can sit here.
- Here is your beef burger. - Thank you.
- Don't grab it. - Okay.
Here is your food.
It looks so tasty, doesn't it?
It's hot, so be careful.
(Order Status)
(All complete)
- They're doing their best. - I know.
I'm shy.
- I feel shy. - Yes.
I'm a bit shy.
- Why? - I'm embarrassed to talk to them.
So, he ordered tteokbokki and a burger.
Pizza has become one of our main dishes now.
Shouldn't he order more to help us out?
Exactly.
I know. He didn't order pizza.
I'm nervous.
(The unintentional test is making the pupil nervous.)
This place is cute.
(And her teacher is waiting for the food.)
I wonder if people are enjoying the food...
as a menu consultant.
(He's nervous too.)
We'll serve the burger with the hamburger.
- No, not the burger and hamburger. - Okay.
- The burger and tteokbokki. - I'm tired.
- Burger and hamburger. - I'm going to do well.
This is for Mr. Matfia.
The road to Matfia.
(To Matfia)
Since he's our teacher,
- should we get him a free ade? - Yes.
- Sure. - Okay.
Okay. Let's do that.
- He's your teacher. - We should do that for him.
(They decided to be generous then be sad.)
But why did he order just two dishes when he's rich?
I know. I don't understand why he ordered just two.
Just get him the ade if you've decided to.
- Why didn't he order the cake? - I know.
Why?
(The dessert team is furious.)
(This teacher-student relationship is funny.)
I'm killing it.
(I'm killing it.)
This is my classic patty.
I'll make a pretty coil for him.
(I'll make a pretty coil for him.)
Please put the sauce on the bun for the beef burger.
Okay.
I'll use the warmest bun.
Nobody gave me a bad review...
after having my tteokbokki.
Nobody.
(Young Ji is getting worried.)
(And so is her teacher.)
Okay.
(The complimentary drink for their teacher is ready.)
- This is the complimentary drink. - Okay.
You should serve it, Gabee.
I don't really know him.
(A brutal mission for the one who hasn't met him)
Everyone's shy around new people.
- Mimi, do you want to go? - Right.
- Okay. I'll get him the drink. - You should go, Mimi.
Do I hold them like this?
- Yes. - Yes.
- I'll be back. - Okay.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Goodness. - These are on the house...
- because you taught us. - Thank you.
- Here. - It's tough, isn't it?
- No, it isn't tough at all. - Really?
- Yes. It's been great. - Really?
You're so pretty.
- Are you a couple? - No.
- You're not a couple? - She's our staff.
- Is that so? - Yes.
- I hope you have a beautiful time. - Thank you.
Please give us a second.
- Young Ji is cooking your dishes. - Okay. Thanks.
(Served the drinks while wishing them a happy date)
(At that moment in the kitchen...)
Young Ji is actually the busiest one.
She's really busy.
Goodness, Young Ji.
(A concerned voice comes from behind.)
I'm fine.
- Young Ji. - Yes?
(Approaching slowly)
- I'm fine. - Your palms are sweaty.
- I'm fine. - These weren't transparent before.
- I'm all good. - Do you need my help?
- I want to help you. Are you okay? - Thanks to you, Gabee...
Thanks to you, I feel comfortable.
You must be having the toughest time.
- No, it's tough for everyone. - It's crazy.
Let's be frank. There's one who has to struggle the most.
- No, everyone is struggling. - Let's be honest.
No.
I'm having the hardest time.
(I'm having the hardest time!)
Right? You are the one who's facing the hardest time.
Thanks.
I told him Young Ji is making delicious dishes.
They'll be ready in two minutes.
Let that old guy wait.
Come and work again tomorrow, Gabee.
I'm busy tomorrow.
You're busy tomorrow.
(Her schedule is too packed to come here again.)
You wanted detox, though.
I'm kind of busy tomorrow.
You have to come.
(The patty for their teacher is getting grilled.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Yes. - Help me with this, Mimi.
- Yes. - I like it.
(The most carefully crafted burger is ready.)
The beef burger is ready.
Yes. I'll head into the enemy territory myself.
- Are you going to see Manager Kwon? - Yes. I made the dish.
It's amazing to meet the chef herself.
- That's right. - I'm going to set them up...
- for you to make one trip. - Yes. I'm ready.
Tteokbokki is ready.
Okay, Neapolitan Matfia.
This tteokbokki is mine and mine only.
- You can take this tray. - Okay. I'll get going.
- Gosh. That cheap guy. Thanks. - See you.
(Approaching the cheap guy...)
(Approaching Manager Kwon resolutely)
- It's Young Ji. - Hello.
(The hall is buzzing as the head chef appears.)
(On her way to her former master, now a customer)
You asked...
- for a 1-on-1 face-off. - Who did?
- I made all of these. - Really?
I can make them in five minutes now.
That was really quick, indeed.
- That was quick, right? - I know.
Goodness.
I came myself.
- You don't serve, then? - Never.
- You look exhausted. - I'm exhausted.
- Please enjoy. - Thanks.
I'll check back on you later.
- They're all tasty, right? - Yes, they are.
- It's good, right? - It's good.
- Where are you from? - We're from China.
Is it tasty?
- It's tasty. - Tasty.
This one has 2 shrimp, but this one has 3.
I'll get the shrimp.
(Exposing their mistake by starting a conversation)
- Mi Hyun. - I think...
- What did he say? - Hold on.
The Chinese customers said, "This one has two shrimp,"
- "but this one has three." - Goodness.
(While making tteokbokki for the global customers...)
(Originally, 3 shrimp fries are placed on tteokbokki.)
They're getting ready. Please wait.
Tteokbokki is ready.
(They served it while missing one shrimp fry.)
(As a result...)
Why does this one have 3 shrimp while this one has 2?
File a complaint.
(The mistake was obvious because they ordered two dishes.)
(Serving it quickly on a tray)
(Entering while catching her breath)
I'm sorry.
- Thank you. - Thanks.
- Please enjoy. - Okay.
- Thanks. - Please enjoy.
- Are you enjoying it? - Yes.
Yes. I knew it.
A chef shouldn't handle it like that.
We should've done it.
Let's all go upstairs...
- and apologize. - I think I served it.
- Shall we? - Okay.
We can't do this.
Gabee, when we cause trouble like this one,
we bow at a 90-degree angle to apologize.
Did it happen before?
You should demonstrate how it's done.
We're truly...
- sorry. - Sorry.
- It's not "My apologies." - We're sorry.
Look devastated.
(They have to look devastated.)
("How to apologize properly" by the floor manager)
We heard the news...
that you were missing a piece of the deep-fried shrimp.
We'll work harder to better serve our customers.
- We're truly sorry. - Sorry.
- It's okay. - We're fine.
- We forgot about it. Sorry. - Yes.
Then please...
- enjoy. - Enjoy.
- Okay. - Okay. Thank you.
(The lecture on "how to make an apology" ends.")
Let's go.
- We always apologize sincerely. - We were sincere.
We apologize sincerely.
- We could feel it. - Sincerely.
They could feel it.
(A sophisticated apology softened the customers' hearts.)
I needed to do something, but I forgot about it...
and went upstairs to mess around.
- It's okay. - Eun Ji.
- Yes? - Yes?
Will you go upstairs...
and see how Neapolitan Matfia is enjoying the food?
Okay.
Check on him later when you serve other dishes.
- No. I'll go upstairs at once. - Great.
I think he came with his girlfriend.
- It looked like a situationship. - It looked like he came...
with someone he's in a situationship with.
Of course, they came together.
- There's something between them. - Exactly.
- There's definitely something. - I knew it right away.
- I know. - Is it a situationship?
- There's something between them. - Really?
- I'm totally sure. - The lady is all glammed up.
- She is... - Today...
It seems she went to a beauty salon.
- Of course. - Really.
- He's interested in her. - Yes.
- It does seem like it. - Also,
do you know what made it more obvious?
He was strangely nicer to me than usual.
I'm the manager here in charge of developing new dishes.
(I'm the manager here in charge of developing new dishes.)
How could they do so well when I taught them only once?
It must be really tough.
(He's strangely different.)
- What? - He's oddly nice to me.
Why?
- I don't know. - Usually, he's not that nice to me.
Really? Did he really do that?
(Tell me more)
(Hurry and tell me)
(And the lady)
(It seemed like she went to a salon)
(So I knew they were in a situationship)
(Singing)
(I have to continue)
(But I have nothing more to say)
(Upstairs in the meantime)
- I'll cut it in half. - Okay.
(It looks like he's cutting steak when it's a burger.)
Cutting a burger isn't easy. You know that, right?
The patty is well-shaped and nicely grilled.
- You have to cut it like this. - Thanks.
(Sharing the beef burger in a sweet manner)
- I'm more curious about tteokbokki. - Let's try it.
(He tries a bite of tteokbokki in a cozy manner.)
(Satisfied)
It's good.
It's working up my appetite. That's not good. It's an emergency.
(Tteokbokki that increases both appetite and love)
I didn't order a lot on purpose...
in case they don't taste good.
- But it's good. - It's tasty.
(He was afraid of their skills to order a lot.)
I should've ordered more.
(Next, he tries the beef burger.)
(Surprised)
- It's good. - Why does it taste good?
It's really good.
(Taking a big bite while whipping around his piercings)
I need to recruit Young Ji and Mimi...
to work at my restaurant.
(Manager Kwon won both love and students.)
- I feel really good. - Gabee.
- We had great reviews. - You should take a break, Gabee.
- No. I'm feeling great. - You need some rest.
- Actually, - Take some rest, Gabee.
- I'm waiting for something. - For what?
I want to try some. I'm just saying.
No. I know you're busy.
- I don't need to try it. - Okay.
- I'm just saying it... - You want to see what it's like?
- because you said you would. - Sure.
- I'm just saying. - Gosh.
I'm just saying.
Don't worry about it.
- It's nothing. - I think I'm hyperventilating.
No. If there are any leftovers,
I'll happily try them.
I told her I was actually looking forward to having some tteokbokki.
(The part-timer has her wrapped around her fingers.)
Sorry. I was just kidding. It was a joke.
(Unlike the shocked boss,)
That was funny.
(Mimi calmly takes action.)
- Mimi. - Try this. It's really good.
(The intense reaction makes her proud.)
She soothed her with some fries.
(Fortunately, her request to try the food is fulfilled.)
Gabee, have you tried the pomegranate ade?
- Yes, I have. - I gave her the deep-fried shrimp.
You have. And the shrimp too.
The dishes I haven't tried are the burgers...
(Burgers and...)
- and tteokbokki. - They're the main dishes.
I can't describe the dish...
- to the customers. - Right.
- I can't tell them, "It's good." - Because you don't know.
- I got it. - But it's okay.
I'm really okay.
(Exhausted)
I'll cook them for you no matter what. Please wait.
- It's perfectly seasoned. - It's tasty, right?
- Nice. - It's really tasty.
It's really tasty, isn't it?
It's so good.
I see. When you said pomegranate ade, did you mean...
- zesty pomegranate ade? - Zesty pomegranate ade?
Goodness. That's right.
- Too much rice cake in a burger - Too much rice cake in a burger
- Patty slid in - Patty slid in
(It's almost a duet now.)
- We'll get one of those. - Okay.
Hello. Would you like to take a look around the pop-up store first?
(The customers are rushing in,)
Please place this on your table.
(but they lead them professionally.)
You can take the utensils on the second floor.
Thank you.
Are you working part-time?
Yes. I'm helping them a bit today.
(Of course, the part-timer is also earning her deep-fried shrimp.)
- These are the bottoms. - Okay.
(The kitchen team is organizing the grilled rice cake buns.)
- That's the last batch of buns. - We need to cut more of them, then.
No, we just need to do it again.
Please let there be more than five.
There will be more than five buns when I open it.
- Why? - I'm okay.
- I'm happy. - You're happy.
- We have an order. - Okay.
We have 1 pizza, 1 tteokbokki,
and a beef burger.
For Table 7, 3 beef burgers, and 1 shrimp burger.
Also, 1 tteokbokki and 1 pizza.
Table 9 ordered 1 pizza, 1 tteokbokki, and 1 shrimp burger.
- Okay. - Because we're out of the buns,
the burgers might take some time.
Okay.
(Burger Order Status: 4 beef burgers and 2 shrimp burgers)
(However,)
(they only have 5 rice cake buns left.)
I really have to do that after doing this.
I need to work on the buns.
I have no choice now.
We have...
no choice now.
You think I can't pull it off. You think I'll fail, don't you?
(Laughing)
- No, we don't think so. - She's funny.
You think I'll fail.
I won't fail. I'm Lee Young Ji.
- Pizza was served. - We'll craft one beef burger first.
- Okay. - Nice.
- I'll cook three beef burgers now. - Okay.
(Chef Mimi takes over.)
- One beef burger is ready. - Okay.
It'll be great to serve the burger with tteokbokki.
- One shrimp burger is ready too. - Okay.
(Burger Order Status: Complete)
(3 rice cake buns are left.)
Young Ji, you really have to work on the buns after this.
We have 3 orders of pizza, which is 1st.
Let's make 3 pizzas. I've never made 3 burgers either.
Let's do this.
Three burgers? Don't worry. I'm here for you.
I'm making pizza all day.
(Making a large quantity as the business flourishes)
She's the pizza lady.
(A generously big pizza)
I'll push them down.
(Pressing down the patties)
I flip them.
(When the strangely flat patties are grilled,)
We'll make large patties now.
(pizzas are baked just in time.)
It's heavy.
It's hot.
Gosh. Nice.
(On the hot pizza,)
(she places basil before slicing it.)
Three beef burgers, right?
Pizza is getting smaller.
- It's true. - The dough...
- It's okay. - The dough was uneven.
(Don't get them wrong. They all weigh the same.)
- Sorry. - It's a bit small indeed.
(It's a bit small.)
(Yu Jin makes a turn.)
It's all up to our chef.
Here are your pizza and burger.
Here's your pizza.
Here's your pizza. I tried one before.
- It's so good. - Is it?
It can be a bit spicy.
But it's deliciously spicy.
(She takes a big bite while holding a slice.)
(Laughing)
- Does it taste good? - Yes.
(Stretching)
The cheese is totally...
(It may be small in size, but it's super chewy.)
- Is Tabasco making it spicy? - Yes.
Anything else special?
- This is fun. - Can I go upstairs?
- It's all right, isn't it? - Yes.
(The part-timer laughs in a high pitch more frequently.)
- This is fun. - Yes.
- So far. - So far.
- Yes. So far. - So far.
(Her body and mind are out of sync.)
- Three beef patties are ready. - Okay.
(Patties are ready.)
(She piles up a tower of burgers.)
- Three beef burgers are ready. - Okay.
(Burger Order Status)
(All complete except for a shrimp burger)
(0 rice cake buns are left.)
(She starts cleaning the grill.)
That's our chef. Let's go.
- It's smoking like crazy. - Gosh.
It's crazy. Yes.
- Add the butter beneath the buns. - Should I do it?
Let them slide like this.
It's just like the buns sold near Gongdeok Station.
(Yu Jin in the meantime...)
- How was it? - It was really good.
- Really? - Why are you so good at this?
- Really? I'll let them know. - Yes.
- I'll tell them. Thanks. Good luck. - Travel safely. Okay.
(Table 7, 3 beef burger combos)
Here are your beef burgers.
(Crashing)
- Are you okay? - I'm sorry.
- It can happen. - Sorry.
- We'll bring a new one right away. - It can happen.
(Holding her breath and diving to the floor)
- Are you all right? - Yes, I am. I'm sorry.
- I'll wipe it quickly. - We'll get you a new one.
(Table 7, 1 crashed beef burger combo)
She's exhausted.
(Puppy Yu Jin, who created a mess, grabs cleaning tools...)
(and wipes the floor.)
Okay. Let's see. I'll be gentle.
(Young Ji, who has no idea,)
Not bad.
(is scratching the grill.)
(Burger Order Status)
(Beef burger, RIP)
Not bad.
(And the rice cake buns are still getting cooked.)
Overall, they're not bad.
- It was so good. Really. - It's delicious, right?
- What's with you? - I know.
Why are you so good?
- Is she your girlfriend? - She's my staff.
- Come on. - Come on. Stop lying.
- What's the point? - His eyes are... What?
- Are you two in a situationship? - She's an employee.
- Come on. - She works at my restaurant.
- The food was good, right? - You're really good at this.
- Really? Give us some feedback. - It was good.
Honestly, I have no complaints. Really.
(You're good on your own now.)
Honestly, I thought it wouldn't taste good,
- so I only ordered 2 dishes. - Right. You ordered 2.
You ordered only two dishes, thinking they wouldn't taste good.
- I was shocked by how tasty it was. - Other dishes are tasty too.
You should have some more.
You should've ordered more for us. Why did you order just a little?
No. I didn't want to trouble you.
- I see. You're so kind. - Thank you, by the way.
Are we on par with Viatoledo?
It's possible if you try a little harder.
- Look how fast you work. - It's not bad, is it?
- It's not bad at all. - I'm really sorry, Young Ji.
- Did you knock it over? - I knocked it over.
- What? - The burger. You haven't heard.
- I haven't. - I went overboard...
and carried three burgers.
- And I knocked over one of them. - Are you hurt?
- No, I'm totally fine. - Okay.
You're so sweet. Thank you. I'm sorry.
How mature of you.
What do you say? I was a good boyfriend.
I actually wanted...
to flick on Yu Jin's head, but I remained a good boyfriend.
- Anyway, good luck. I'll get going. - Okay. Take care.
Thank you.
Thank you. It's all thanks to you.
- You can do this, Gabee. - Bye.
That was a lie. It's all thanks to me.
(She's kidding. Thank you for your help, Manager Kwon.)
Yu Jin, did you let them see you fall?
Come on. I showed them all right.
- Did you show them? Good job, then. - Yes.
Then one more beef burger, Yu Jin?
Yes. We need 1 beef burger and 1 shrimp burger.
- Sorry. That's right. - Right? One more beef burger.
(Coming up next)
(Space Rice Cake is in chaos again today.)
(I'm crying.)
(In the end, the head chef ends up flat on the floor.)
(Appearing before exhausted Earth Arcaders...)
Good morning. What?
(is the third part-timer of Space Rice Cake.)
- Kyung Soo. - Hello, Young Ji.
(Doh Kyung Soo, the director of KKPP Food)
(With a professional, the kitchen finally settles down.)
(You'd better not mess it up.)
(Director, I won't let you down.)
(A director who's got both charisma and sweetness)
(Being next to you makes my heart flutter.)
(Space Rice Cake just got a whole lot sweeter.)
(The secret dish he's here to teach them)
(On top of crispy rice crackers)
(Exotic ingredients to bring in more flavor)
(Rice cracker tacos)
(It's delicious.)
(A unique charm that draws in not only the Earth Arcaders...)
(but also the customers)
(Kicking off the service with confidence)
(Or so we thought...)
(Didn't they order tacos?)
(I forgot to put them in.)
(Young Ji, I ruined one. I'm sorry.)
(Hey, Kyung Soo)
(Mistake after mistake right from the start)
(The Earth Arcaders get betrayed by the person they trusted.)
I'm the worst.
(What fate awaits part-timer Do Kyung Soo?)
(Space Rice Cake)